There's a gentleman you sleep with animal. You have the urge for animals.
okay, come, urge for animal, as if you...
abuse the animal anytime, anywhere.. so please come up. Jesus. Love you.
I'm the young man you said that I have the urge for animal.
I used to see animal in my dream, and I slept with them...
Come here
You mean you sleep with animal.
Yes! Man of God.
Any animal that just made the sound (the call), your urge was so serious that you grabbed them.
Man of God deliver me. Please!
How did you come about sleeping with your animal ?
I don't know !
Deliverance in Jesus' name
Standard for Life
people of God Emmanuel ! ( God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Thank you very much.
My name is Wisdom Linus. I come from Calabar, Nigeria
The problem that brought me to SCOAN was having the urge for animal.
The problem started last year, in August.
I'm a chef by Profession; I cook for people at hotels or at their homes.
I was employed in Calabar, to cook for a lady.
in the compound there was a dog and I was the one who fed the dog;
after cooking, I would give the dog food.
One terrible night, I had a dream where I saw the dog with my picture.
Inside the dream, I beat the dog saying, "What are you doing with my picture?"
From then, the following morning, I began to have affection for the dog,
as if it's my girlfriend.
All my human affection was dead; my feelings were for the dog alone.
When everybody has gone to bed, at the time I was supposed to release the dog...
to do its duty, I would take the dog to my room when I was about to sleep.
Then, we would sleep together as boyfriend and girlfriend.
This had become a habit and because of the problem, I could not concentrate.
Sometimes, the urge would come after seeing the dog in the dream;
I would not be able to concentrate in the kitchen and I would make terrible mistakes.
I would put too much salt or flavouring and before I knew it, they sacked me.
The affection would happen like this;
when the dog would come in the dream the next day,
Everything around me would resemble the dog; I would see the dog every minute and every second -
both physically and spiritually.
That was how my focus was on the dog alone, not on human beings.
The feelings I had for the dog, were the feelings a person is supposed to have for a girlfriend.
For how long you've been having this problem ?
Close to one year now.
Sometimes, I would realise that my affection was supposed to be for human beings, not for an animale;
If it come to my room because he would come to my door, I would chase the dog away.
After that, he come attack me in my dreams.
The following day, I would succumb to my feelings for the dog again.
I have prayed and visited several churches where I complained to many pastors;
they told me to fast and pray but my urge for animals continued.
Tell us how do you receive your deliverance ? How do you get to know about Emmaneul TV ?
The way I received my deliverance began through watching Emmanuel TV.
Because I love watching the channel so much and seeing the way the man of God delivering people;
evil spirits would manifest and speak about who they are.
I realized that it was my turn to be delivered because my urge was not normal.
I came last Sunday and to my greatest surprise, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied,
"There is a young man who has a affection for animals".
I knew I was the one he was talking about, so, I came out.
The man of God stretched his hand towards me, and I fell.
From that moment, I do not have affection for animals any longer.
That night the man of God prayed for me, the dog attacked me in my dream.
The dog was carrying my picture, running up and down.
The next thing I saw was Prophet T.B. Joshua snatch the picture from the dog and that was the end.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me, I saw fire come out of my head
and I began to feel light, instantly.
Once again, let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus Christ
My advice to the whole world is this:
When you experience things in life, don't take them for granted
and don't run from God; run to God.
because He's the only one who can deliver you.
SCOAN is the place to be, I've confirmed it. Praise the Lord !
We just want to advise, now God almighty as delivered you...
Nothing happens for nothing, and nothing comes by chance.
What happened to you was caused by sin.
Now God almighty as delivered you...Please make sure you give all your life for Christ and accept Him with all your hearts.
Make His word a standard for your life.
I will pray that God almighty in His infinite Mercy will grant you the grace to be far from sin, and be close to His Word in Jesus name>
Amen !
The best is yet to come in your life in Jesus name !
Let us put our hands together for our Lord Jesus !
Standard for Life
My name is Wisdom Linus. I come from Akwa Ibom, Nigeria
The Lord has done a mighty thing in my life since last week, when I came here.
God Almighty used Prophet T.B. Joshua to save my life, by delivering me
form what I have passed through for the past eight years now.
I thank God; I'm so grateful because I really enjoy my stay at the SCOAN.
I give God all the glory in Jesus name.
A spirit was tormenting me for the past eight years; it was a spirit that gave me the urge for animals.
Since last Sunday, Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied to me and delivered me,
I don't have such feelings anymore and I know that I am free.
Thank God that the Lord Jesus has visited me and my family and we are set free in Jesus' name.
So what are we(you) actually doing before coming down to the church ?
I have not been working.
Sometimes, I asked people for help; other times, I washed cars in order to eat.
I had to struggle before I came here and received my deliverance.
Okay, so I've heard it from our brother, our brother was set free from an Evil spirit...
that really pushed him to have an urge for animals.
Apart from pushing him into such a terrible act. It also really destroyed his life.
Especially (destroyed) his career as a chef and also his finances and everything connected to him
But we give glory to God that he has been set free.
Since coming to SCOAN. We've had the wonderful testimony of the changes in his life.
So, brother, we are here today with a message from Prophet TB. Joshua
The man of God prophet TB Joshua said that he wants to present to you a gift on behalf of himself and Emmanuel TV partners worldwide.
To really really encourage you now to start a new life in Christ, Jesus
So we're here to present to you this gift of two hundred thousand Naira (200,000 Naira)
While we can see the display of emotion from our brother
Mr Wisdom receives cash gift of 200,000 Naira from T.B. Joshua & Emmanuel TV partners
I am so grateful; thank You, Jesus !
I thank God so much. I'm so grateful. I know that my family has been set free.
With this gift, I'll come back with great testimony in the mighty name of Jesus. I'm so grateful.
Because I wasn't expecting this, I'm so grateful. Thank you senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, my mentor.
May God bless you in the mighty name of Jesus. I'm so grateful. Thank you, Jesus.
Hallelujah ! that is the sum of two hundred thousand Naira for our brother !
On behalf of Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners.
And we're also presenting to him the word of God
The mirror as a reminder for him to make the word of God a standard for your life
As you are going out now? You are going to make the word of God the standard for your life and maintain this deliverance you've received.
Amen ! Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus !
I ask God to give me the grace to maintain this deliverance to help my siblings.
I'll work hard, to make sure this blessing will manifest very well my family and my life in the mighty name of Jesus.
Amen, we thank God for your life,
and we pray that God would give you the grace to maintain all these wonderful Blessings...
he received here at the SCOAN by making the word of God the standard for your life.
We know the best is yet to come in Jesus man.
Amen ! Thank you, Jesus. Thank you. Jesus. Thank you, Jesus !